<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Game</string>

    <string name="game_title">Judul Game</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="csgo_details">Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS: GO) expands upon the team-based action gameplay that it pioneered when it was launched 19 years ago. CS: GO features new maps, characters, weapons, and game modes, and delivers updated versions of the classic CS content (de_dust2, etc.).</string>
    <string name="csgo_title">Counter-Strike Global Offensive</string>
    <string name="cs2_description">Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS: GO) expands upon the team-based action gameplay that it pioneered when it was launched 19 years ago. CS: GO features new maps, characters, weapons, and game modes, and delivers updated versions of the classic CS content (de_dust2, etc.).</string>
    <string-array name="game_name">
        <item>Counter-Strike Global Offensive 2</item>
        <item>Dota 2</item>
        <item>Little Nightmares 2</item>
        <item>Asassins Creed 2</item>
        <item>Left 4 Dead 2</item>
        <item>Age Of Empires 2</item>
        <item>Portal 2</item>
        <item>Half-life 2</item>
        <item>Team Fortress 2</item>
        <item>Payday 2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="game_description">
        <item>"Counter-Strike took the gaming industry by surprise when the unlikely MOD became the most played online PC action game in the world almost immediately after its release in August 1999," said Doug Lombardi at Valve.</item>
        <item>One Battlefield. Infinite Possibilities. When it comes to diversity of heroes, abilities, and powerful items, Dota boasts an endless array—no two games are the same. Any hero can fill multiple roles, and there an abundance of items to help meet the needs of each game. Dota doesnt provide limitations on how to play, it empowers you to express your own style</item>
        <item>Return to a world of charming horror in Little Nightmares II, a suspense adventure game in which you play as Mono, a young boy trapped in a world that has been distorted by the humming transmission of a distant tower. With Six, the girl in the yellow raincoat, as his guide, Mono sets out to discover the dark secrets of The Signal Tower. Their journey won’t be easy; Mono and Six will face a host of new threats from the terrible residents of this world. Will you dare to face this collection of new, little nightmares?</item>
        <item>Assassin’s Creed® 2 is the follow-up to the title that became the fastest-selling new IP in video game history. The highly anticipated title features a new hero, Ezio Auditore da Firenze, a young Italian noble, and a new era, the Renaissance.</item>
        <item>Set in the zombie apocalypse, Left 4 Dead 2 (L4D2) is the highly anticipated sequel to the award-winning Left 4 Dead, the #1 co-op game of 2008. This co-operative action horror FPS takes you and your friends through the cities, swamps and cemeteries of the Deep South, from Savannah to New Orleans across five expansive campaigns.</item>
        <item>Age of Empires II: Definitive Edition celebrates the 20th anniversary of one of the most popular strategy games ever, now with stunning 4K Ultra HD graphics, and a fully remastered soundtrack. Age of Empires II: DE features “The Last Khans” with 3 new campaigns and 4 new Civilizations. Frequent updates include events, additional content, new game modes, and enhanced features with the recent addition of Co-Op mode!</item>
        <item>Portal 2 draws from the award-winning formula of innovative gameplay, story, and music that earned the original Portal over 70 industry accolades and created a cult following.</item>
        <item>1998. HALF-LIFE sends a shock through the game industry with its combination of pounding action and continuous, immersive storytelling. Valve debut title wins more than 50 game-of-the-year awards on its way to being named "Best PC Game Ever" by PC Gamer, and launches a franchise with more than eight million retail units sold worldwide.</item>
        <item>The most highly-rated free game of all time! One of the most popular online action games of all time, Team Fortress 2 delivers constant free updates—new game modes, maps, equipment and, most importantly, hats. Nine distinct classes provide a broad range of tactical abilities and personalities, and lend themselves to a variety of player skills.</item>
        <item>PAYDAY 2 is an action-packed, four-player co-op shooter that once again lets gamers don the masks of the original PAYDAY crew - Dallas, Hoxton, Wolf and Chains - as they descend on Washington DC for an epic crime spree. The CRIMENET network offers a huge range of dynamic contracts, and players are free to choose anything from small-time convenience store hits or kidnappings, to big league cyber-crime or emptying out major bank vaults for that epic PAYDAY. While in DC, why not participate in the local community, and run a few political errands?</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="game_photo">
        <item>@drawable/cs2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/dota2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/littlenightmare2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/assassinscreed2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/l4d2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/ae2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/portal2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/hl2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/tf2_cover</item>
        <item>@drawable/payday2_cover</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>